恩 你已经完成了
Alright, you're done!
我们看一下解决方案
Let's take a look at the solution.
对于天气（指match后的Weather类型），我们只要获得一个可读的数据库，
For weather,
we just get a readable database and
然后向其传递ContentProvider调用(query调用)中的所有参数
pass all of these parameters
from the content provider call.
天气和地点的实现方法是相当类似的
The solution for weather and
location is pretty much the same.
对于每一个从ContentProvider传往query的参数
For each one, we're going to pass the
parameters that come through the content
我们都传递到可读的数据库的query方法中去
provider into the query function
of our readable database.
再次提醒 这些参数是从ContentProvider中来的
Again, these are the parameters that
come through the content provider, and
这些参数是我们要传递给数据库的
these are the parameters that
we pass into the database.
地点（指match后的Location类型）看起来是类似的
Location looks approximately the same.